There's a signal bleeding through the walls tonight
오늘 밤 벽을 뚫고 신호가 새어 나와.
A voice that lost its name before the morning light
아침이 오기 전에 이름을 잃은 목소리.
The dial keeps spinning past the empty bands
다이얼은 텅 빈 채널들을 지나 계속 돌아가.
Where someone left a message no one understands
아무도 알아들을 수 없는 메시지를 누군가 남겨둔 곳.
And the wires remember what the world forgot
그리고 전선들은 세상이 잊은 것을 기억해.
Every word still burning in a frequency left to rot
모든 말들이 썩도록 내버려진 주파수 속에서 여전히 타오르고 있어.
We were the broadcast no one tuned to hear
우리는 아무도 들으려 채널을 맞추지 않은 방송이었지.
A wavelength dissolving into atmosphere
대기 속으로 녹아드는 하나의 파장.
The static holds the shape of what we said
잡음은 우리가 말했던 것의 형상을 담고 있어.
A forgotten frequency still ringing in my head
잊힌 주파수가 여전히 내 머릿속에 울려 퍼져.
The tower stands but nothing transmits anymore
송신탑은 서 있지만 더 이상 아무것도 송신되지 않아.
Just rust and rain collecting on the studio floor
스튜디오 바닥에는 녹과 비만이 고여 있을 뿐.
I found the reel still loaded in the deck
나는 릴이 여전히 데크에 걸려 있는 것을 발견했어.
Your voice preserved in dust and magnetic wreck
먼지와 망가진 자기장 속에 보존된 너의 목소리.
And the wires remember what the world forgot
그리고 전선들은 세상이 잊은 것을 기억해.
Every word still burning in a frequency left to rot
모든 말들이 썩도록 내버려진 주파수 속에서 여전히 타오르고 있어.
We were the broadcast no one tuned to hear
우리는 아무도 들으려 채널을 맞추지 않은 방송이었지.
A wavelength dissolving into atmosphere
대기 속으로 녹아드는 하나의 파장.
The static holds the shape of what we said
잡음은 우리가 말했던 것의 형상을 담고 있어.
A forgotten frequency still ringing in my head
잊힌 주파수가 여전히 내 머릿속에 울려 퍼져.
We were the broadcast no one tuned to hear
우리는 아무도 들으려 채널을 맞추지 않은 방송이었지.
A wavelength dissolving into atmosphere
대기 속으로 녹아드는 하나의 파장.
The static holds the shape of what we said
잡음은 우리가 말했던 것의 형상을 담고 있어.
A forgotten frequency still ringing in my head
잊힌 주파수가 여전히 내 머릿속에 울려 퍼져.